mibr8352@colorado.edu 720-253-6660

Summary

Adaptable and high achieving computer science undergraduate. Possesses a wide range of technical skills and is a strong object-oriented programmer. Computer science tutor. Member of cyber security club. Seeking internship position. Experience includes several years of customer service jobs as well as recruiting and training of sales associates. Loves working with a team.

Education:

<u>University of Colorado Boulder</u> , Boulder CO	2018-2022
Field of Study: Computer Science	GPA: 3.7

Cherokee Trail High School, Aurora CO

2014-2018

Recognized for GPA and completion of International Baccalaureate program

GPA 4.0

Work Experience

Computer Science Tutor, BOLD Center, University of Colorado

September 2019-Present

Support underrepresented students in STEM fields.

Assist students on assignments and projects.

Java Tutor, Self employed

June 2019-Present

- Guide a student through assignments and projects in Java language.
- Work with a student to break down essential concepts of object-oriented programming.
- Lead student to an "A" on every assignment.

Caterer, University of Colorado Events Planning and Catering

August 2018-Present

- Work on a team to keep a clean kitchen while preparing food for large events.
- Communicate with clients to ensure complete satisfaction with our service.
- Pre-set, deliver and maintain food for 100+ attendee events.
- Meet food safety standards.

Assistant Manager, Vector Marketing

June 2018- August 2018

- Created and revised sales pitch to drive higher volume sales.
- Number one in office sales- built a customer base of 100+ and sold over \$20,000 in direct sales.
- Recruited and trained team of successful sales associates.

Salad Artist, Mad Greens

December 2016- August 2017

- Maintained clean kitchen, dining area, and restrooms.
- Prepared food for customers while meeting food safety standards.
- Worked as a team to get tasks done efficiently.

Technical skills:

- Strong programmer in C++ and Java.
- Intermediate in HTML and CSS
- Learning MySQL, x86-64, and Python
- Learning full-stack website development
- Search engine optimization
- Creating web applications (ask me for some of my past projects!)
- Proficient in Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, Powerpoint)
- Proficient in Salesforce
- Creating sales pitches
- Intermediate Spanish
- Working with special-needs adults (volunteer at Adam's camp)

Personal Attributes:

- Strong presenter
- Adaptable and resilient
- Time management
- Personable and strong communicator
- Fast and self directed learner

References:

Testimonial from Shawn Senna, tutee:

I recently embarked on my senior year at Regis University in the Computer Information Systems program, and as part of it, was required to enroll in several senior level Computer Science courses. Coding does not come naturally to me, and the prerequisites I took for these classes were taught in a different language, so naturally I was floundering a bit. Thankfully Michael was available to walk me through the extensive homework assignments each week. Thanks to his help, not only did I receive A's on all of my coding assignments, but I walked away with a much better understanding of the content each week. Additionally, the shared-screen, remote tutoring method that he employs, I found to be extremely convenient and effective. I would absolutely recommend Michael for Computer Science tutoring! **Contact:** (720)-435-6542

CU Catering Contact: (303) 492-8833, Stephanie Grant Vector Marketing Contact: (720) 496-5715, Cory Schott

MadGreens Contact: (720) 213-3665, Amber

BOLD Tutor Contact: (303) 492-176, Chantal Bacca